you are teleporting all the time from
moment to moment to moment to moment but
you are doing it in a sense frame by
frame by frame by frame instead of
understanding that you can actually well
to use a colloquial phrase you can
actually skip some of the frames
how do you skip them by understanding
what you're doing to begin with
you have to understand the mechanism
before you can use the mechanism in a
different way so a deeper understanding
of the fact that you're already doing
that
will allow you more opportunity to see
how you can skip some of the frames so
to speak you're not really skipping
frames but that's the way it will feel
the idea is to live in the present not
be in a hurry to get somewhere else or
be something you're not at the moment
and just act on your passion to the best
you're able with no insistence on what
the outcome should look like because
that's what keeps raising your vibration
and raising your vibration is what
allows you to understand and have the
what epiphany
of how to see the structure of what
we're talking about and see more clearly
what it is you're already doing and see
how to use what you're already doing in
a different way because when you can see
the structure more clearly through the
Epiphany vibration then you can
understand that space and time are your
side effects they're your Illusions and
they become more flexible and more
malleable and then you have an insight
as to how you can use them in a
different way to make it appear as if
you are teleporting farther and farther
distances the thing you have to
understand is that distance is an
illusion it doesn't really exist
everything is here and now so you have
to really wrap your mind around that
concept deeply enough so that it's
ingrained within you that you're not
actually going anywhere
in a sense you're just recreating a
different location here